[
    {
        "front": "> Topics: 3D, Effects, Export, Keyframes, Project and Composition Settings",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q1. What type of light never casts a shadow in a 3D scene?</b>\n- Parallel\n- Ambient\n- Point\n- Spot",
        "back": "Ambient"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q2. Where do you change the shutter angle for the motion blur in a composition?</b>\n- on the Basic tab of the Composition Settings dialog box\n- on the Advanced tab of the Composition Settings dialog box\n- on the 3D Renderer tab of the Composition Settings dialog box\n- in the File > Project Settings dialog box",
        "back": "on the Advanced tab of the Composition Settings dialog box"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q3. What is a null object?</b>\n- a special layer used to hold expressions\n- an invisible layer that has all the properties of a visible layer so it can be parented to any layer in the composition\n- a solid layer with a black background that can be parented to any layer in the composition\n- a visible layer that can be parented to any layer in the composition",
        "back": "an invisible layer that has all the properties of a visible layer so it can be parented to any layer in the composition"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q4. What adjustment in the Lumetri Color effect can help restore edge detail to footage?</b>\n- Contrast\n- Clarity\n- Sharpen\n- Intensity",
        "back": "Sharpen"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q5. Where can you control the settings for footage created from an After Effects composition?</b>\n- Render Queue panel\n- Save As dialog box\n- Export Queue panel\n- Progress panel",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q6. Which blur effect supports the use of a depth matte to define the focal range?</b>\n- Camera Lens Blur\n- Bilateral Blur\n- Smart BlurS\n- Channel Blur",
        "back": "Camera Lens Blur"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q7. How can you create a direct relationship between two layer properties?</b>\n- Use the pick whip to enable Parenting.\n- Use grouping.\n- Use Value Linking.\n- Use the pick whip to enable Connecting.",
        "back": "Use the pick whip to enable Parenting."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q8. Which technique is useful for creating slow-motion, fast-motion, freeze frame, or other retiming results for a layer?</b>\n- Time Remapping\n- Time Displacement\n- Posterize Time\n- CC Wide Time",
        "back": "Time Remapping"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q9. An image was created on a transparent background in Photoshop using different dimensions to this After Effects composition. Which option was used when importing the PSD file shown below to place the image at its original scale and position?</b>\n- Click Import As > Composition.\n- Click Import As > Footage.\n- Click Import As > Composition \u2013 Retain Layer Size.\n- Set the PSD sequence option.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q10. How can you render a file in the background and keep working in After Effects?</b>\n- Click File > Export > Add to Adobe Media Encoder Queue.\n- Click File > Watch Folders.\n- Click File > Export > Background Render.\n- Click File > Export > Add to Render Queue.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q11. What properties are added to a 3D layer? (Select three items.)</b>\n- Z Rotation\n- Anchor Point\n- Material Options\n- Position\n- Geometry Options",
        "back": "Z Rotation\nAnchor Point\nPosition"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q12. You want to include controls from an After Effects composition in the Essential Graphics panel. What is one way to do this?</b>\n- Command+click (Mac) or Ctrl+click (Windows) a property in the Timeline to add it to the Essential Graphics panel.\n- Select Add Formatting.\n- Drag a property from the Timeline into the Essential Graphics panel.\n- Double-click a property in the Timeline to add it to the Essential Graphics panel.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q13. You have applied the Auto Levels effect but notice flickering in the results. How can you reduce this?</b>\n- Adjust the Black Clip property.\n- Increase the Blend with Original property.\n- Increase the Temporal Smoothing property.\n- Adjust the White Clip property.",
        "back": "Increase the Temporal Smoothing property."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q14. Which type of light is used in this scene?</b>\n- Ambient\n- Spot\n- Point\n- Parallel",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q15. Which effect recovers alpha-channel detail from a scene keyed by a typical keying effect, including recovering detail lost due to compression artifacts?</b>\n- Keying > Advanced Spill Suppressor\n- Keying > Key Cleaner\n- Keying > Extract\n- Keying > Keylight (1.2)",
        "back": "Keying > Key Cleaner"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q16. If you want to apply an effect to multiple layers and adjust all layers at once, which method should you use?</b>\n- Use the layer pick whip to link properties.\n- Parent the layer controls.\n- Use an adjustment layer.\n- Set one layer effect and then copy and paste its results to the other layers.",
        "back": "Use an adjustment layer."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q17. You want to scale all elements in a composition, including the composition itself. How can you do this?</b>\n- Click File > Scripts > Double-Up.jsx.\n- Link all layers and then change the composition settings.\n- Click File > Scripts > Scale Composition.jsx.\n- In the Composition Settings dialog box, scale the composition dimensions and the layers will scale to match.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q18. Holding the Shift key when rotating a 3D layer constrains the rotation to how many degrees?</b>\n- 20\n- 30\n- 45\n- 15",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q19. How can you choose which frame of a composition to show as a thumbnail image for the composition in the Project panel?</b>\n- Select the desired frame in the Composition Settings dialog box.\n- Move the playhead to the desired frame and click Composition > Set Poster Time.\n- You cannot change the thumbnail image.You cannot change the thumbnail image.\n- From the Render Queue, go to Render Settings to set the thumbnail image.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q20. When you want to add properties to the Essential Graphics panel, how can you easily see only the supported properties?</b>\n- Type \"PP\" twice with the Timeline panel active.\n- Click the Solo Supported Properties button in the Essential Graphics panel.\n- Switch to the Essential Graphics workspace.\n- All properties are supported by the Essential Graphics panel.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q21. You want to take an existing layer and make it into two separate layers. How can you do this so the separation occurs at the playhead?</b>\n- Click Layer > Split Layer.\n- Click Edit > Duplicate.\n- Click Edit > Extract Work Area.\n- Click Edit > Split Layer.",
        "back": "Click Layer > Split Layer."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q22. How can you create a single composition from multiple footage items?</b>\n- Select the items and click File > New Project.\n- Select the items and click Composition > New Composition from Selection.\n- Drag the selected footage items to the Create a New Composition button at the bottom of the Project panel.\n- Select the items and click Composition > New Composition.",
        "back": ""
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q23. You attach a video monitor to view your color correction. Where can you configure the monitor\u2019s preferences?</b>\n- Preferences > Output\n- Preferences > Video Preview\n- Preferences > Video Hardware\n- Preferences > Previews",
        "back": "Preferences > Video Hardware"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q24. A file is in the Render Queue but cannot be rendered. You see that it is labeled Needs Output. What should you do?</b>\n- Save the project.\n- Set an output file name from the Render To menu.\n- Set an output file name and location from the Output To menu.\n- Adjust the composition settings.",
        "back": "Set an output file name and location from the Output To menu."
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q25. Which effect cannot be applied to a mask shape?</b>\n- Path text\n- Fill (close path only)\n- Smear (open path only)\n- Stroke",
        "back": "Smear (open path only)"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q26. What type of object creates a single-color layer for use as a backdrop?</b>\n- Footage\n- Solid\n- Mask\n- Null Object",
        "back": "Solid"
    },
    {
        "front": "<b>Q27. What is the maximum number of masks that can be applied to a single layer in an After Effects 7.0 composition?</b>\n- 512\n- 256\n- 128\n- 127",
        "back": "127"
    }
]